###### Princess Dental Staffing

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

_Last updated: November 18, 2024_

Princess Dental Staffing offers various services to help its users find dental staff and coordinate dental employment opportunities in the dental community. Princess Dental Staffing’s Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is designed to explain the information we collect and how we use it to provide our services and give users a better experience. It applies to any users of [www.PrincessDentalStaffing.com](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/) and any web pages, mobile applications and mobile websites operated by Princess Dental Staffing (collectively, the "Site"), including those who are seeking to find dental professionals through Princess Dental Staffing ("Employers") as well as those who are looking to promote their profiles through Princess Dental Staffing ("Candidates"), and any users of any of the various services that Princess Dental Staffing or its subsidiaries provide through the Site or any other channels, including over the telephone (collectively, "Services"). Please note that certain of our subsidiaries have separate privacy policies.

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms "Princess Dental Staffing," "we," "us," and "our" refer to Princess Dental Staffing, Inc. You" refers to you, as a visitor or user or the Site or the Services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to third party entities that may use the Site or Services. Such entities’ use of the Site and Services are subject to separate terms that they agreed to when they registered or otherwise contracted with Princess Dental Staffing. Other capitalized terms that are not expressly defined in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as set forth in the Princess Dental Staffing [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms).

By using the Site and/or the Services, you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

I. Information We Collect and their Sources
-------------------------------------------

How we collect and store information depends on the Services you use and the activities in which you participate. You can use some of the Site and Services without providing any information other than that automatically collected as described below.

Visitors who access and browse the Site without registering are "Site Visitors." In order to utilize some of the Services offered by Princess Dental Staffing, you must register with Princess Dental Staffing. All users who register with Princess Dental Staffing are "Registered Users."

### A. Information you provide

Regardless of whether you are a Site Visitor or a Registered User, all information that you provide to us when registering, posting a job, posting a profile, communicating through the Site, discussing options over the phone, utilizing our mobile applications or that you otherwise provide on the Site or by phone, email, postal mail or otherwise, will be stored by us. You represent and warrant to us that you have the right and authority to provide us all information you provide about yourself or others. You may provide us with information in various ways, including:

#### 1\. When registering

When you register directly through Princess Dental Staffing, we will collect and store the information that you provide to us on our online registration forms. This may include, among other information, your:

* first and last name
* email address
* home address
* gender
* phone number

Some users may have the opportunity to register with Princess Dental Staffing by connecting through a third-party application programming interface (API). Please see Section I.B.4 below to learn about the information we access, collect and store if you register with Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party provider.

If you register for a Service that requires you to pay a fee, Princess Dental Staffing will also collect your payment method details, such as account number, expiration date, and security code, as well as your billing address for payment purposes, if not previously provided.

#### 2\. When posting a job

If you are a Employer, we collect and store all of the additional information that you provide to us on your job posting or that is otherwise included in an auto-generated job posting. This may include, among other information:

* the type of candidate you are looking for, your schedule, location, hourly rate, narrative job description and/or requirements (such as software competency)
* pictures you choose to provide
* health information, if you choose to provide it
* any other information you choose to include in your job posting

#### 3\. When posting a profile

If you are a Candidate, we collect and store all of the additional information that you provide to us in your profile. This may include, among other information:

* your training and licensure, your availability, your location, your level of education, languages you speak, your ability to drive
* related services you provide
* pictures you choose to post
* your phone numbers
* references, if you choose to provide them
* any other information you choose to include in your profile

#### 4\. By telephone

Both Site Visitors and Registered Users may provide information to Princess Dental Staffing when they contact Member Care or utilize certain Services Princess Dental Staffing may offer by telephone. For example, if you call Princess Dental Staffing to discuss options over the phone, we will collect and store all of the information you chose to provide to us, including but not limited to financial information, information about the needs of your office, requirements of the professionals you seek, etc. If you provide information about someone other than yourself, you represent that you have authority to do so.

#### 5\. Otherwise through the Site or by telephone, email, postal mail or chat

Certain Registered Users may provide additional information on the Site through other Site features and offerings such as our online communication platforms, groups and payment platforms. In some cases, Site Visitors may have the ability to provide us information through the Site, such as contact information. In addition, both Registered Users and Site Visitors may choose to provide information by phone, email, postal mail, or chat. We collect and store all of the information you provide us through these channels. Moreover, if you provide information about someone other than yourself through any of these channels, you represent that you have authority to do so.

### B. Information provided by others

#### 1\. By Site Visitors, Registered Users and others

Princess Dental Staffing also captures and collects information that Site Visitors, Registered Users and others provide about one another. For example, Candidates may invite Site Visitors, Registered Users or others to rate and indicate their relationship to the Candidate on the Site. Additionally, certain Registered Users may post reviews about individual Candidates. Princess Dental Staffing may also obtain and post audio recordings of Candidate references, which may also be accessed from the Site. In addition, certain Registered Users may communicate directly with one another through Princess Dental Staffing platforms. Site Visitors, Registered Users and others also may provide us information about Registered Users by phone, email or postal mail. Princess Dental Staffing captures and stores all information it receives from Site Visitors, Registered Users and others about other Registered Users and Site Visitors.

#### 2\. By third parties to verify your information and representations

In order to promote the safety and integrity of the Site and Service, you authorize Princess Dental Staffing, as provided in the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms), to utilize third party service providers to check your information on an ongoing basis against a variety of sources, which may include, but are not limited to, state licensing boards, national criminal databases, sex offender registries, certain media streams, terrorist watch lists, criminal and fugitive watch lists, fraud watch lists, law enforcement reports, and other data to assist us in verifying the information you provide us (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) and the representations and warranties you make in the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) and on the Site (such as representations regarding your criminal background).

#### 3\. By third parties that perform background checks

As provided in the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms), we may provide some or all Registered Users and Site Visitors with the ability to request from a third-party consumer reporting agency that a background check be run on themselves or on Candidates they are considering hiring using information that they and any subject Candidates may provide. Any such background checks will be subject to the terms we establish for such checks on the Site pages where they are requested or authorized, the terms of this Privacy Policy, and our [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms). Princess Dental Staffing may receive a copy of, or otherwise have access to, any such background check, unless otherwise specified in this Privacy Policy or the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms).

#### 4\. If you connect to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party authentication provider

You may have the opportunity to authenticate with Princess Dental Staffing through Apple, Facebook, or Google when you register for Princess Dental Staffing or after you have registered for Princess Dental Staffing. If you connect to Princess Dental Staffing through one of these providers, we will collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information you agreed the provider could share with Princess Dental Staffing. Your agreement (and our access to your information) takes place when you instruct, accept or allow the authentication provider to register you for a Princess Dental Staffing account or otherwise connect to Princess Dental Staffing through the provider. The information Princess Dental Staffing may access, collect and store may include the following, among other information, as allowed by you:

* your full name
* your profile picture
* your email address
* your gender
* your location (i.e. city)
* the names and pictures of friends or connections
* your interests and affinity networks
* other information you make publicly available

#### 5\. By service providers you use in connection with our Services

If you engage a provider through Princess Dental Staffing, such as a dental hygienist or dentist, that provider may provide us with information about you, such as information relating to your interactions with the provider.

#### 6\. By other sources

In addition, we may obtain information about you from other sources (e.g., partners, researchers, marketers, etc.), such as demographic data, and other information to enable us to comply with regulatory requirements, ensure the accuracy of data, better understand your likely interests, prevent fraud, etc. We may combine information that we collect from you with information about you from such other sources and use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### C. Information you expressly authorize us to collect

We may from time to time request permission to collect certain information from or about you. For example, if you use a Princess Dental Staffing mobile application, we may request permission to access information about the contacts listed in your mobile device phone book when you initiate an address book search for friends who have downloaded the application. We may also request permission to access and store your location (e.g., your precise GPS-based functionality on the mobile devices used to access the Site and Services). If you grant your permission, we will access and/or store such information unless you subsequently opt out by adjusting the settings in your mobile device. See your device manufacturer’s instructions for further details.

### D. Automatically collected information

We may automatically collect certain information about the computer or devices (including mobile devices) you use to access the Site and Services as described in this section below.

#### 1\. Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer and mobile device

When you visit the Site, Princess Dental Staffing receives the internet protocol ("IP") address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the internet), your computer operating system, the type of web browser you are using, and browser language. If you are using a mobile device, Princess Dental Staffing may also receive unique device identifiers and other information about your mobile or other device(s), and mobile operating system. We may correlate this information with other information we have about you. We may also automatically collect information related to the ways in which you interact with the Site and the Services, such as referring and exit pages, URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages and content viewed (including ads viewed) and the order of such views, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time you use the Services, error logs, and other similar information.

#### 2\. Cookies and other technologies

A cookie is a tiny data file that resides on your computer, mobile phone, or other device, and allows us to recognize you when you return to the Site using the same computer (or mobile device) and web browser. Like most websites, we and our service providers use cookies, and tracking pixels to track Site usage and trends, evaluate the effectiveness of our ads both on and off our Site, customize your experience on the Site and improve the quality of our Services. For example, using these technologies we can determine, among other things, which pages of our Site you visit and which ads you click on. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser settings to decline cookies. In some cases, however, doing so may impact your ability to use Princess Dental Staffing. Tracking pixels do not identify individual users, and the analysis of data obtained by tracking pixels is performed on an aggregate basis.

When you visit our website, log in, register or open an email, cookies, ad beacons, and similar technologies may be used by our online data partners or vendors to associate these activities with information they or others have about you, including your email address. We (or service providers on our behalf) may then send communications and marketing to these email addresses. You may opt out of receiving this advertising by visiting [GetEmails](https://app.getemails.com/optout).

Princess Dental Staffing places 3rd party cookies on their website to serve ads on ad networks like Google, Doubleclick, and other networks.

Princess Dental Staffing advertises to all customers that opt-in through a form on our site. Your info will never be sold.

#### 3\. Online analytics and advertising

When you visit our Site or open one of our emails, we may allow authorized third parties, such as ad servers, ad agencies, ad exchanges, ad technology vendors, and research firms, to place or recognize a unique cookie, pixel, and/or similar technologies on your browser in order to provide you relevant Princess Dental Staffing advertisements as you surf the Internet. These advertisements may be targeted to you based on information these authorized third parties know or infer about you and include in the cookies placed on your browser, and/or on information about your Internet browsing activities gathered through your browser. If you prefer not to receive these online behavioral advertisements, you may opt-out. In order for the opt-out to work, your browser must be set to accept third party cookies. Furthermore, if you buy a new computer or mobile device, change web browsers or delete the opt-out cookie, you will need to perform the opt-out task again. Please note that if you opt-out you may continue to receive Princess Dental Staffing advertisements as you surf the Internet, including contextual ads based on the content on a webpage you are visiting. However, these advertisements will not be displayed based on information contained in, or collected by, cookies or other technologies placed on your browser when you visit our Site or open our emails.

We also use Google Analytics to measure Site usage and improve our visitor experience. The relevant data is provided to us by Google in the aggregate (i.e., individual users are not identified) and allows us to better understand our Site audience. The Google Analytics features implemented by us allow us (i) to evaluate and generate reports on certain demographic, behavioral, and interest metrics of users collected by Google, and (ii) to create advertising remarketing audiences and campaigns based on such metrics, which may be segmented into aggregated groups.

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings form at [https://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

**Do Not Track Notice.** Some browsers used to access the Internet may give you the option through "Do Not Track" settings associated with such browsers to request that a website operator not track your information across its website or other websites. We engage in such tracking in order to optimize and/or customize our Services, detect and respond to allegations of fraud, and to otherwise ensure the safety of our Registered Users and Site Visitors. While we do not currently honor such browser requests, we will not use your information in a manner that violates this Privacy Policy. In addition, you retain the ability to opt out of certain online analytics and advertising activities as discussed in this section above.

#### 4\. Social media features and widgets

Our Site includes social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook "Like" button and the Facebook"Share" button. These features may collect your IP address, the URL of the page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

II. Purposes For Which We Use Information
-----------------------------------------

In general, the information we collect is used for our business purposes: (1) to improve our Services and enhance your experience with Princess Dental Staffing, (2) to enable us to provide a safer community for all of our Registered Users, and (3) to help us communicate with you. For example, we may use your information to:

1. register and service your account;
2. include in Employer profiles, job postings and Candidate profiles;
3. contact you in response to questions and solicit feedback and input from you;
4. notify you about new features of the Services, special events, or products, services, and special offers, or other information that we believe will be of interest to you via email, SMS messages, or other media or networks;
5. administer sweepstakes and contests;
6. enable Employers with each other and with Candidates to search based on the information the other has made available on the Site, and information others have provided about them;
7. connect Employers with Candidates that appear to meet their needs and preferences;
8. enable Registered Users to search for, find, interact, connect and share information with other Registered Users they may have an interest in interacting with;
9. enable Registered Users who connect to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party provider to see which of their friends/connections are Registered Users, or friends with other Registered Users;
10. verify information you provide us as well as the representations and warranties you make to us in the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) or on the Site;
11. perform analytics and research aimed at improving the accuracy, effectiveness, usability, or popularity of the Services;
12. generate and review reports and data about our user base and usage patterns, including to improve the content and features of the Services or develop new Services;
13. otherwise help protect the safety and integrity of the Site and Princess Dental Staffing users; and
14. personalize promotional messages or content on the Site, via email or other ads on Princess Dental Staffing or third party sites.

We may aggregate and/or de-identify information collected by the Site, the Services, or via other means so that the information is not intended to identify you. Our use and disclosure of aggregated and/or de-identified information is not subject to any restrictions under this Privacy Policy, and we may disclose it to others without limitation for any purpose.

III. How We Share and Categories of Third Parties With Whom We Share Information
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

In addition to using the information collected by Princess Dental Staffing for the purposes described above, we may also share your information with various third parties, as described below. Please review our sharing policy closely. By using our Site or our Services, you agree to allow us to share the information you provide to us in the ways described below. Your ability to make changes to what information is shared is described below in Section IV.

### A. With All Site Visitors and Registered Users

If you are an Employer or a Candidate, in order to increase your chances of finding a job or finding the help you need, we share with Site Visitors and Registered Users the information that is included in your job posting or profile, which may include your contact information, as well as the following registration information, which we may include in your job posting or profile: your first name, first initial of your last name, city, state, profile picture, and if you are a Candidate, your gender and, unless you opt-out, your age or experience. With certain exceptions, you choose how much detail you want to include in either your job posting or your profile. We may also share on your profile or job posting any company reviews you have posted on our Site, whether you have connected to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party provider, and any connections you have with other Princess Dental Staffing members, including the nature of those connections. If you are a Candidate and have elected to verify certain information with Princess Dental Staffing or to have a background check performed, we may also disclose that information in your profile as a Registered User in addition to your response rate and any payment or payroll preferences you have indicated.

If you post information in a Princess Dental Staffing online group forum that information may be viewed by any Site Visitor or Registered User who accesses the forum.

We may display personal testimonials of Registered Users and other endorsements on our Site or in other marketing materials. These testimonials or endorsements may include information such as the Registered User’s first name, first initial of last name, town and state. With a Registered User’s consent, we may include their full name.

### B. With other Registered Users and corporate providers

In addition to the information that is provided to all Registered Users and Site Visitors, Candidate and Employer reviews and references are made available to certain Registered Users and Site Visitors. If you are a Candidate, your phone number may be visible to certain Registered Users if you elect to provide it in your profile. In addition, your approximate residential location (through Google map plotting) is made available to certain Registered Users and Site Visitors unless you elect to keep that information confidential.

If you are an Employer or a Candidate, you will appear in search result listings if you match the search criteria used by a Candidate or Employer, as applicable. Similarly, you may appear in emails sent to Candidates or Employers in your area. Employers may opt-out of being included in Candidate search results and in certain emails sent to Candidates. In addition, if you are an Employer and you view the profile of certain Candidates, those Candidates may be able to see that you have viewed their profiles.

If you are a Registered User, your Princess Dental Staffing online status may be made available to other Registered Users unless you elect to keep that information confidential.

If you connect to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party authentication provider, we may allow any of your friends/connections who have connected to Princess Dental Staffing to see that you are a Registered User. In addition, other Registered Users who have connected to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party authentication provider will be able to see if you are friends with any of their friends or if you share certain affinities or interests with them.

In addition, if you provide information about someone other than yourself, you represent that you have authority to provide us the information and to authorize us to share the information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Notwithstanding the foregoing, a Candidate may share information about who is receiving their services, including contact information, with Princess Dental Staffing and any subsidiaries. Such shared information would be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**If we terminate your registration for any reason, we reserve the right to send a notice of your termination to other Registered Users with whom we believe you have corresponded.**

### C. With vendors/service providers

We also share information with vendors with whom we have a contractual relationship and who perform services for Princess Dental Staffing including, without limitation, vendors who provide email, demographic information, or geo-location information services, vendors who perform background checks or screenings, vendors who process or accept credit card payments, vendors who run classified advertising businesses, vendors who send SMS messages to Registered Users’ mobile phone numbers, vendors who provide services that enable us and other third parties to detect and prevent fraud, in each case to the extent applicable. In certain cases (such as for vendors who help facilitate our online communication services or provide fraud detection and prevention services), the information we share may include the contents of written and audio messages you send through our online communication platforms.

We have implemented Google’s Invisible reCAPTCHA technology on our site. Use of the Invisible reCAPTCHA is subject to the [Google Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and [Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/).

### D. With listings in and through Google and other public search engines, social media sites (e.g. Facebook, LinkedIn, Google), and on other third party websites)

In an effort to further facilitate the ability of Employers or Candidates to find help or a job, selected information contained in Employer job postings and Candidate profiles, which may include photo, first name, first initial of last name, city, state, and job/provider description, may also be shared with third party search engines, social media sites, and other third party websites or vendors who run classified advertising and other businesses, and thus may be listed in third party web site search results and on third party websites, which would make that information available to the public and allow them to link to your Princess Dental Staffing posting. Registered Users can opt-out of some options by adjusting their Account Settings. If you post information in a Princess Dental Staffing online group forum, your content, including your name as the contributor, may be displayed in third party search engine results and available to the public.

### E. With third-party authentication providers if you connect to Princess Dental Staffing through them

If you connect to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party authentication provider, you may elect to post certain of your activities on Princess Dental Staffing back to your third-party account. You will be prompted to decide whether or not to share those Princess Dental Staffing activities.

### F. As required by law or for reasons of safety

We may disclose your information when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is appropriate in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the health or physical safety of any person, violations of this Privacy Policy, the [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms), and/or to protect the rights and property of Princess Dental Staffing, our employees, users, and the public. This may involve the sharing of your information with law enforcement, government agencies, courts, and/or other organizations.

### G. With our affiliates

You acknowledge and agree that we may disclose any of the information we’ve collected about you to any of our affiliates or subsidiaries for the purposes of providing you with the Services, operating the Site, soliciting you for potential employment opportunities with those affiliates or subsidiaries, and our other commercial purposes, including those of our affiliates and subsidiaries.

### H. With Your Consent

We also may share your information with a third party if you consent to the sharing.

### I. Background Checks

Princess Dental Staffing may offer various background check services from consumer reporting agencies. A Candidate can authorize a Motor Vehicle Records Check, Criminal Records Check, Criminal+ MVR Check, or an Investigative Criminal Plus check in response to a request by an Employer who is considering hiring him or her. If you authorize a background check to be run on you in response to a request by an Employer who is considering hiring you, the results of the check will be shared directly with the Employer. If you are a Registered User who has requested a background check through Princess Dental Staffing, a statement may be included in your profile to confirm that you have completed that check. The service provider who completes the background check may also send the results to you by email or postal mail. **You acknowledge that sensitive material may be included in your background check, and that you are responsible for providing us and our service provider (if applicable) with correct information.**

Through certain pages of the Site, Princess Dental Staffing may from time to time offer to individuals who may or may not be Registered Users the opportunity to purchase Investigative Criminal or Investigative Criminal Plus background checks on caregivers who may or may not be Registered Users. If you authorize an Investigative Criminal or Investigative Criminal Plus Check to be run on you in response to such a request, the results of the check will be shared directly with the requester. If you are a Registered User of the Site and have requested such a background check, a statement may be included in your profile to confirm that you have completed that check. However, we will not share the check or results with any other Site Visitor or Registered User unless you specifically consent. The service provider who completes the background check may send the results to you by email or postal mail.

### J. Business transactions

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge and consent that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s affiliates may continue to process your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

IV. Your Choices Regarding the Sharing of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------------------------------------

Registered Users have control over what optional information they choose to share with us when utilizing our Services (such as pictures, certain details in a job description or profile, etc.).

In addition, Registered Users have the following opt out choices with respect to the sharing of their information, which they can manage via their account settings:

* Registered Users can opt out of having their Princess Dental Staffing online status visible to other Registered Users who are on Princess Dental Staffing.
* Registered Users can opt out of having information contained in their job postings or candidate profiles shared with other Registered Users.
* Registered Users who have connected to Princess Dental Staffing through a third-party authentication provider may subsequently opt out of having certain information shared with Princess Dental Staffing and certain of their Princess Dental Staffing information shared with the provider by disabling the connection in their account settings.
* Registered Users who have opted into receiving text message alerts notifying them of account related events can opt out of receiving those text messages.
* Candidates can opt out of having their approximate residential location (through Google map plotting) visible to Registered Users by not providing their address.
* Users of a Princess Dental Staffing mobile application, who have given Princess Dental Staffing permission to access certain information from their mobile device such as their location or contacts or camera, may subsequently opt out of that information sharing by adjusting the settings in their mobile device.

Your opt out preferences will take effect within 10 days of receipt of your request.

V. Your Communication Choices
-----------------------------

By becoming a Registered User, you are consenting to receive certain email communications from us, such as special offers, tips and advice, notifications of new Employers or Candidates in your area, customer surveys and administrative notices.

You have a choice at any time to stop us from sending you emails for marketing purposes by adjusting your settings in your account settings or using the opt out option on the correspondence. You also have the option to opt out of receiving certain other emails from Princess Dental Staffing, such as certain educational emails, by adjusting your settings in your account settings. Go to your account settings for a complete list of the email types you may opt out of receiving. You can also opt out of commercial email messages by following the "unsubscribe" link included in these messages. Please note that despite any indicated email marketing preferences, we may continue to send you administrative emails regarding Princess Dental Staffing, including, for example, notices of updates to our Privacy Policy, notifications of new Employers or Candidates in your area, responses to job postings from Candidates, and responses to job applications from Candidates, if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner

You may also opt-out of receiving unsolicited marketing calls from us regarding your Princess Dental Staffing account by notifying us by email or chat.

If you have opted in to receive SMS messages from us but would now like to opt out, you may do so by adjusting your settings in your account settings.

If you are an Employer, certain Candidates may initiate contact with you directly using the messaging features of the Princess Dental Staffing Site. You have an option at any time to stop permitting Candidates from initiating contact with you by adjusting your settings in your account settings.

VI. Changing or Removing your Personal Information and Closing your Account
---------------------------------------------------------------------------

You can update certain of your information by logging into your account and accessing your account settings. If you would like to remove some of the information you have posted on the Site, such as information you posted in profiles and job postings, you may do so by editing or deleting that item in your My Profile & Settings area or your My Jobs area.

If you no longer wish to participate in our Services, you may inactivate your account directly through your account settings.

If you inactivate your Princess Dental Staffing account, we will remove your name and other contact and identifiable information from our publicly viewable database. If you inactivate your account, we have no obligation to retain your information, and may delete any or all of your account information without liability. However, we may retain information related to you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, de-identified information, account recovery, auditing our records, enforcing our rights and obligations under our agreements, or if required by law. Princess Dental Staffing may also retain and use your information if necessary to provide the Services to other Registered Users. For example, just as an email you may send to another person through an email service provider resides in that person’s inbox even after you delete it from your sent files or close your account, emails you send through Princess Dental Staffing to other Users, as well as your contributions to Princess Dental Staffing groups, may remain visible to others after you have closed your account. Similarly, other information you have shared with others, or that others have copied, may also remain visible. Princess Dental Staffing disclaims any liability in relation to the deletion or retention (subject to the terms herein) of information, or any obligation not to delete the information. Princess Dental Staffing does not control when search engines update their search index or cache, which may contain certain job posts, profiles or other information that have since been removed from Princess Dental Staffing’s Site.

VII. Your Data Protection Rights
--------------------------------

You have numerous rights in connection with your personal information and how we handle it, i.e to access, correct, update or request deletion, object the processing, restrict processing, request portability, withdraw your consent and right to file a complaint.

Your rights:

* To access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information. You may do so by contacting us at [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com).
* To object to the processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict the processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information. You may do so by contacting us [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com).
* If we are processing your personal information with your consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted pursuant to lawful processing grounds other than consent. You may do so by contacting us at [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com).
* You have the right to file a complaint with a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority.
* You can control and limit the type of personal information we collect and process about you in a number of ways. For example, you can disconnect your social media account(s) from your account or control your social media privacy settings to limit the information shared with us. You can also reset your mobile advertising identifier or limit ad tracking altogether using the settings on your phone. You can also limit or disable the use of cookies (or similar technologies).

We will respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

VIII. Collection of Information from Children
---------------------------------------------

Princess Dental Staffing’s Site and Services are not intended for individuals under the age of 14. Moreover, if we become aware that we have collected personal information (as defined by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) from children under the age of 13, we will take reasonable steps to delete it as soon as practicable.

IX. How We Protect Information
------------------------------

We have implemented a variety of administrative, technical, and physical security measures to protect against the unauthorized access, destruction, or alteration of your information. These safeguards vary based on the sensitivity of information that we collect, process, and store and the current state of technology.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot guarantee that information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

X. Links to Other Websites
--------------------------

The Site and Services may contain links to third-party websites and services. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those web sites or services, nor are we responsible for the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site and Services; thus when you use a link to go from the Site or Services to a third-party web site or service, this policy is no longer in effect and the privacy policy of such third-party site or service will govern.

XI. Changes to Our Privacy Policy
---------------------------------

Princess Dental Staffing reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) at any time. We will notify you about and provide you with choice about material changes to this Privacy Policy or in our practices as required by applicable law. Material changes will go into effect 30 days after we notify. Non-material changes or clarifications will take effect immediately upon posting of the updated policy on our Site. You should periodically check https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/privacy for updates. Your use of the Site or the Services after such effective date will constitute acceptance by you of such changes.

XII. Privacy Information for California Residents
-------------------------------------------------

If you are a California resident, California law requires us to provide you with some additional information regarding how we collect, use, and share your "personal information" (as defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA")).

**Categories of personal information we collect.**

Throughout this Policy, we discuss in detail the specific pieces of personal information we collect from and about our users. Under the CCPA, we are also required to provide you with the "categories" of personal information we collect as defined by California law. The categories we collect depending on the types of services you use are:

* identifiers (such as name, address, email address);
* commercial information (such as transaction data);
* financial data (such as payment method details and billing address);
* internet or other network or device activity (such as browsing history or usage information);
* geolocation information (e.g., your approximate location based on IP address, or precise location with your consent);
* inference data about you (e.g., the additional services or advertising we think would be of most interest to you based on your interactions with us);
* professional or employment-related data (e.g., if you are a Candidate, your references and employment history);
* education information (e.g., if you are a Candidate, your level of education);
* legally protected classifications (such as gender or information obtained from a background check, where applicable);
* physical characteristics or description (e.g., photos you choose to upload to your job postings or profile);
* sensory or visual information (e.g. if you provide us this information in connection with senior care planning or child care)
* medical information (e.g. if you provide us this information in connection with COVID-19)
* other information that identifies or can be reasonably associated with you (e.g., registration and log-in information).

Please note that specific pieces of your personal information may belong to more than one of the above referenced categories.

**How we source, use, and share these categories of personal information.**

We source, use, and share with third parties the categories of personal information we collect from and about you consistent with the various business and operational purposes we discuss throughout this Policy and for the business and operational purposes of our service providers in accordance with the CCPA. See the "Information We Collect And their Sources", "Purposes For Which We Use Information" and "How We Share and Categories of Third Parties with Whom We Share Information" section(s) above for more information.

Please note that the CCPA sets forth certain obligations for businesses that "sell" personal information to third parties. We do not engage in such activity and have not engaged in such activity in the past twelve months from the effective date of this Policy.

**CCPA Rights Disclosure.**

If you are a California resident, the CCPA allows you (or an authorized agent acting on your behalf) to make certain requests related to your personal information. Specifically, the CCPA allows you to request us to:

* Inform you about the categories of personal information we collect or disclose about you; the categories of sources of such information; the business or commercial purpose for collecting your personal information; and the categories of third parties with whom we share/disclose personal information. Such information is also set forth in this Policy.
* Provide access to and/or a copy of certain personal information we hold about you.
* Delete certain personal information we have about you.
* Provide you with information about the financial incentives that we offer to you, if any.

The CCPA further provides you with the right to not be discriminated against (as provided for in applicable law) for exercising your rights. Please note that certain information may be exempt from such requests under California law. For example, we need certain information in order to provide the Services to you. We also will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before responding to a request. In doing so, we may use one or more of the following methods: (i) using your login credentials to verify you (it being understood that we may also ask you to reauthenticate yourself), or (ii) matching two or more data points provided by you with data points maintained by us. If we are unable to verify you through the foregoing methods, we shall have the right, but not the obligation, to request additional information from you. If you would like further information regarding your legal rights under California law or would like to exercise any of them, or if you are an authorized agent making a request on a user’s behalf, please contact us at [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com).

**Shine the Light Disclosure.**

The California "Shine the Light" law gives residents of California the right under certain circumstances to request information from us regarding the manner in which we share certain categories of personal information (as defined in the Shine the Light law) with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We do not share your personal information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

XIII. Privacy Information for Nevada Residents
----------------------------------------------

Under Nevada law, certain Nevada consumers may opt out of the sale of "personally identifiable information" for monetary consideration (as such terms are defined under Nevada law) to a person for that person to license or sell such information to additional persons. If you are a Nevada resident and you have purchased services or products from us, you may submit a request to opt out of any potential future sales under Nevada law by contacting us via e-mail at [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com). Please note we may take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request.

XIV. Contact Us
---------------

If you have any questions on our Privacy Policy, you can contact us via email at [info@princessdentalstaffing.com](mailto:info@princessdentalstaffing.com) or at:

Princess Dental Staffing, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
11445 E Via Linda, Suite 2-629  
Scottsdale, AZ 85259

Princess Dental Staffing
------------------------

(844) 700-JOBS

###### For Candidates

###### For Employers

###### Our Temping Agencies

###### Our Company

* * *

* Copyright © 2008–2024 Princess Dental Staffing. All rights reserved.

Princess Dental Staffing provides a platform to help employers and candidates connect. Princess Dental Staffing does not employ, recommend or endorse any candidate or employer, nor is it responsible for the conduct or damages caused by any candidate or employer. Individual users are solely responsible for screening and selecting appropriate candidates or employers for themselves and for complying with all applicable laws in respect to any working relationship they may establish.

##### Your account is not active.

Sorry, you can't do that because your account is not currently active. Please complete and submit your profile to activate your account.

Crop & Rotate Your Image
------------------------

Done

We're about to open this job on another site…
---------------------------------------------

but before you go, enter your email to receive more job opportunities like this!

Your email address required

By registering, you acknowledge you've read and agree to the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/privacy).

Skip this and take me to the job

##### Plan Upgrade Needed

Sorry! Your plan does not allow you to do that. Please upgrade your plan to enable that functionality.

You are currently on the **Basic (Free)** plan.

Log in to your account

Email Address

Password

Remember sign in for 60 days

* * *

Don’t have an account? [Sign up](#sign-up-665273)

Sign up for an account

Get started with just an email address!

Email Address

By registering, you acknowledge you've read and agree to the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/privacy).

* * *

Already have an account? [Sign in](#sign-in-665273)

Log in to your account

Email Address

Password

Remember sign in for 60 days

* * *

Don’t have an account? [Sign up](#sign-up-584693)

Sign up for an account

Get started with just an email address!

Email Address

By registering, you acknowledge you've read and agree to the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/terms) and [Privacy Policy](https://www.princessdentalstaffing.com/privacy).

* * *

Already have an account? [Sign in](#sign-in-584693)

Success

Error

Warning

Notice
